Misha Demidenko

Core Skills

PHP/HTML/JS



Frameworks



EQ

Advanced

 communicative and listening skills

Strong problem-

solving thinking and skills

Self decision-

 making and quick adaptation

Languages

- English Full professional proficiency
- Russian Native proficiency

Education

PHP Developer

iOS Developer

Psychology in Business

Current location and contacts

- Warsaw, Poland
- @allwellnow
- □ awnisbackwork@gmail.com
- in <u>mishademidenko</u>
- +48 571358971

Software Developer

Summary

Hello! I'm a Full Stack Developer (mostly focused on backend) with a Psychological and iOS development background, and a passion to solve problems and achieve results and goals. Nothing motivates me more than complicated tasks with an observable result upon completion. I believe that my values and experience can help both growing and stable companies in their journey further

Skills:

- PHP (7.2, 7.4, 8.3) / HTML5 / CSS3
- JavaScript/jQuery/AJAX
- MySQL/SQL
- AWS S3 / Lunix server
- OOP MVC / MVVM architectures

Additional:

- REST API / Open API
- Git
- Laravel
- Vue.js
- Atlassian stack / Agile methodologies
- Apache tech
- Swift (Xcode, Ulkit, SwiftUI), Dart / Flutter

Projects - iOS and Web

- Intermittent Fasting App
- Stocks Prediction App with Twitter API Betting Info Hub with Authentication,
- Admin Dashboard, and Verified Betting Links

Detailed iOS portfolio available on GitHub:



github link

Experience

Full Stack Web Developer (Jan 2024 - Present)

Web Solutions LTD, Catania, Italy

Responsibilities:

- · Develop and maintain robust betting ecosystems using PHP, jQuery, and AJAX
- · Implement dynamic user interfaces with HTML, JavaScript, and occasional CSS
- · Collaborate with cross-functional teams to design, develop, and deploy new features
- Work with MySQL and SQL databases to retrieve, pass and insert data
- Utilise AWS S3 for scalable storage solutions
- · Optimise application performance and ensure high-quality user experiences
- · Troubleshoot and resolve technical issues promptly to maintain system reliability

iOS Developer (Dec 2022 - Dec 2023)

Self-funded

After 5 months of learning, I've decided to write a complete project to solidify my knowledge and gain new skills in a practical environment

Result:

Intermittent Fasting App, available on the AppStore

Detailed information on this and other projects of mine you can find in my portfolio using the link above

Marketing Generalist (Mar 2022 - Aug 2022)

Gold's Yacht Company, Dubai, UAE

Besides core Marketing responsibilities on this job, an important point to mention is:

 Outsource teams management - management of 3 teams, processes optimization, creation and control of goals and KPIs for each team

As a **major result**, I consider establishing analytics and report systems with outsource teams as well as 15% average growth on marketing channels

Education

PHP Developer (Sep 2023 - Present)

Self-taught with courses, professional literature, and documentation

iOS Developer (Aug 2022 - Sep 2023)

Self-taught with courses, professional literature, and documentation

Master of Psychology, Psychology in Business (Sep 2019 - Jun 2021)

National Research University «Higher School of Economics», Moscow